{
    "id": "11540553b0094a95963b051be5032b11",
    "title": "Agreements And Disagreements Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0cd375f5c6d144e1b40e11e2c91c330d",
            "title": "Agreements And Disagreements",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "‘You don’t like him.’ ‘Yes, I ………………’",
                    "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "don't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘She doesn’t have a job.’ ‘……………………, she doesn’t.’",
                    "description": "Agreements with negative statements are made with ‘No + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t / not’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Yes",
                        "No"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘It is a great film.’ ‘No, it …………………..’",
                    "description": "Disagreements with affirmative statements are made with ‘No + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t/not’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "isn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rocky cannot swim. ……………………… can I.",
                    "description": "Negative additions to negative statements are made with nor / neither + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "So",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She wasn’t late but you ……………………..",
                    "description": "Affirmative additions to negative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary.",
                    "answers": [
                        "were",
                        "weren't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘He is drunk.’ ‘No, he ……………………..’",
                    "description": "Disagreements with affirmative statements are made with ‘no + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t/not’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "isn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He can speak German very well. ……………………….. can I.",
                    "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "So",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘He won’t come again.’ ‘Yes, he ………………………’",
                    "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘I didn’t break it.’ ‘Yes, you ……………………..’",
                    "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tom wasn’t there. ………………………… was his brother.",
                    "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with ‘nor / neither + auxiliary + subject’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Neither",
                        "So",
                        "Either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I loved the movie but my brother ………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘You don’t know him.’ ‘Yes, I …………………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}